
Q1: Why might we consider Git?

We may consider using Git because it is a good way to store code and allow collaboration between different people.

Q2: What field could data science be applied to? Give an Example.

One field that data science could be applied to is medicine. It could be used to predict which patients are at risk for a certain disease and could be used for population health. 